<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
    <changelog>
        <element>com_redirectfixer</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.3</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Fixed the form structure to remove the extra nested form and support a flat structure where articles can be listed multiple times.</item>
            <item>Fixed incorrect language strings related to article counts and notifications.</item>
            <item>Corrected the language string displayed in the view to properly show the number of articles found.</item>
            <item>Fixed the array structure passed to the fix all articles function inside the model.</item>
            <item>Moved the input value outside of the conditional statement in the template so the cancel button works even when no articles need fixing.</item>
            <item>Properly implemented data binding to the form inside the model.</item>
            <item>Properly implemented loading form data inside the view file.</item>
            <item>Properly implemented the article count number display using the appropriate language string.</item>
            <item>Updated the fix method to reduce structural duplication and normalize data into <![CDATA[$validarticles]]>.</item>
            <item>Removed throw statements to avoid early exit when a single article update fails.</item>
            <item>Used the model's setError method to accumulate error messages and allow the controller to enqueue them properly.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>Removed unused <![CDATA[getTable()]]> and <![CDATA[getItem()]]> methods from the model.</item>
            <item>Implemented proper data structuring inside <![CDATA[loadFormData()]]> using user state data.</item>
            <item>Updated the toolbar authorization retrieval to follow the modern Joomla! approach.</item>
            <item>Simplified the default view file by removing unnecessary constructors and global variables.</item>
            <item>Switched to a flat table structure allowing articles to appear multiple times.</item>
            <item>Moved normalized article logic from the controller into the model.</item>
            <item>Separated processing logic into a protected method to remove duplication between <![CDATA[updateAllArticles()]]> and <![CDATA[updateSingleArticle()]]>.</item>
            <item>Updated the controller statement used to fetch the model.</item>
            <item>Corrected configuration language strings to better describe malformed URL functionality.</item>
            <item>Removed unnecessary global variables from the model and constructor.</item>
            <item>Replaced manual checked out validation with the <![CDATA[BaseDatabaseModel::isCheckedOut()]]> method.</item>
            <item>Removed the application global variable from the model and limited user state handling to only required statements.</item>
        </change>

        <note>
            <item>This release focuses on structural cleanup, Joomla! modernisation, code optimization & bug fixes.</item>
        </note>
    </changelog>
</changelogs>
